Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series F: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: Miscellaneous and Photographs, / Date(s): 1940-2001 (inclusive) -- 1940-1963 (bulk); F000; / Quantity: 3 boxes; 1 oversize folder / Dimensions: 4 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries FC: GSD Posters, / Date(s): 1990-2001; Folder: FC019; / Quantity: 70 items / Dimensions: varies / Medium: print / Support: paper
City and Regional Planning Student Directory, 1978-1979 / Directories AB003
City Planning: A Comprehensive Analysis of the Subject Arranged for the Classification of Books, Plans, Photographs, Notes, and Other Collected Material / Publications EA065, EA068, EA069, EA091
City Planning Will Lose Recognition / Clippings BA005
Classification for Books and Plates / Typescripts EA063
Class Members Attending Reunion / Lists (document genres) BC151
Class of 1950, 50th Reunion / Booklets BC128
Class of 1955, 50th Reunion / Booklets BC129
Class of 1959, 40th Reunion / Booklets BC130
Class of 1959, 40th Reunion / Folders (containers) BC131
Class of 1959, 40th Reunion / Xerographic copies BC132
Class of 1960, 40th Reunion / Booklets BC133
Class of 1960, 40th Reunion / Folders (containers) BC134
Class of 1963, 40th Reunion / Booklets BC135
Class of 1964, 40th Reunion / Booklets BC136
Class of 1965, 40th Reunion / Booklets BC137
Class of 1975, 25th Reunion / Booklets BC138
Class of 1975, 25th Reunion / Folders (containers) BC140
Class of 1979, 20th Reunion / Booklets BC141, BC143
Class of 1979, 20th Reunion / Folders (containers) BC144
Class of 1979, 25th Reunion / Booklets BC142
Class of 1987, 10th Reunion / Booklets BC146
Class of 1987, 15th Reunion / Booklets BC145
Class of 1992, 10th Reunion / Booklets BC147
Class of 1994, 10th Reunion / Booklets BC148
Class of 1995, 10th Reunion / Booklets BC149
Clothes Make the Woman / Articles BA014
Cluny Collection / Brochures CC040
Cluny Collection / Newsletters BC074
Cobb will Chair Architecture Department / Clippings BA005
Colleges Urges to Act on Cities / Correspondence BA002
Commencement Ceremony, 1981 / Programs (documents) DC017
Commencement Ceremony, 1983 / Programs (documents) DC017
Commencement Ceremony, 1995 / Programs (documents) DC018
Commencement Week Program / Programs (schedules) FA030
Commencement Week Program, 1995 / Programs (documents) DC018
Commencement Week Program, 1997 / Brochures FA056
Comments on Report by Ruth Cook / Reports EA055
Common Landscape of America, 1580-1845 / Notebooks EA099
Community Assistance Program Publications / Brochures CB001
Community Service Program / Clippings FA048
Connection / Newsletters BC026
Connection / Press releases BA001
Contemporary American Architect: Don M. Hisaka / Reprints BD013
Continuing Professional Education Program / Brochures DB007
Could This be Times Square Tomorrow / Clippings FB026
Course Descriptions, 1982 / Course descriptions AA031
Cross-Registration Procedures / Leaflets (printed works) FA024
Current Conditions and Academic Planning Issues: Discussion Paper / Plans (reports) AA019
Current GSD Catalog, 1982 / Typescripts AA032
David Adler Archive: Finding Aid / Finding aids EA110
Dean's Annual Report, 1980-1981 / Annual reports AA015, AA023
Dean's Annual Report, 1981-1982 / Annual reports AA023, AA033
Dean's Annual Report, 1982-1983 / Annual reports AA016, AA023
Dean's Annual Report, 1983-1984 / Annual reports AA023
Dean's Annual Report, 1985-1986 / Annual reports AA022
Dean's Annual Report, 1986-1987 / Correspondence AA021
Dean's Annual Report, 1987-1988 / Annual reports AA020
Dean's Annual Report, 1989-1990 / Annual reports AA024
Dean's Annual Report, 1990-1991 / Reports AA045
December, 1982 / Posters DB078
Dedication of Gund Hall / Typescripts DA014
Demands by Student-Faculty Assembly / Press releases DB002
Department of Visual and Environmental Studies: Visiting Faculty and Guest Lecturers 1996/97 / Brochures FA066
Description of a Film Documenting the Construction of Gund Hall / Correspondence EB003
Design and Public Policy / Press releases DB043
Design for Tourism and Leisure / Newsletters BC037
Design Professors Seek Dean's Ouster / Clippings AA011
Design Research Story / Booklets DB011
Design School Given $2 Million for Construction of New Center / Manuscripts DA012
Design Thinking / Notebooks EA099
Design with Nature / Photostats DC054
Development of the New Architecture / Typescripts DB052
Development Program / Brochures DB007
Development Program / Xerographic copies BB008
Development Program: The New Building / Brochures BB031
Development Program: The New Building / Pamphlets EB020
Development Program: The Seed of that Better Reality / Memorandums BC007
Development Program Bulletin, Harvard Graduate School of Design / Bulletins BC021
Dewey Classification for Frances Loeb Library / Envelopes EA062
Do's and Dont's for Solicitors / Typescripts BB002
Don M. Hisaka and Associates Selected to Undertake Gund Hall Repairs / Press releases AA038
Downtown Revitalization Studio: The Urban Designer and the City Process / Interviews CA008
Draft Courses of Instruction in the Faculty of Design / Leaflets (printed works) FA023, FA024
Dutch Architect Takes Starring Role / Articles BA017
Eckbo, Halprin, Sasaki, Haag: a Retrospective / Correspondence BC119
Economics of Neighborhoods / Interviews CA008
Education of Planners: with Special Reference to the Graduate School of Design of Harvard University / Publications AA066
Eisenman - Alexander Debate / Newsletters CA012
Eleanor Raymond Architect / Notebooks EA099
Elections of Departmental Representatives and a General Council of the Graduate School of Design / Speeches BC061
Elias Torres: A Selected Bibliography / Clippings FA048
Environmental Design and its Arbiters / Typescripts DC010
Envisioning the City / Clippings FA031
Eric Owen Moss: a Bibliography / Brochures FA040
Eternal See-Saw / Newsletters BC031
Eternal See-Saw / Typescripts DB052
Evaluation: 'Gray Elephant' in Harvard Square / Publications BB039
Evaluation: No One Is Neutral about Gund Hall / Publications BB039
Evening Courses for Professional Development (1986) / Booklets DB123
Executive Education Seminars / Booklets CB005
Exhibitions and Lectures / Posters AA037
Expanding Frontiers of Architecture / Typescripts DB052
Exploring (New) Urbanism Proceedings / CD-Rs BB035
Faculty Publications / Lists (document genres) BB040
Fall 1985 Lecture Series / Brochures DC019
Fifty Years in Retrospect: Brief Account of the Origin and Development of the ASLA / Correspondence CC128
Financial Aid Policies, 1981-1982 / Booklets AB006
For'm / Journals (periodicals) AB004
Forsite / Publications CC145
Frances Loeb Library / Brochures EA082, EA096
Frances Loeb Library. Collections Inventoried for NHPRC Project, 1984-1985 / Correspondence EA137
Frances Loeb Library. Harvard Graduate School of Design / Brochures EA132
Frances Loeb Library. Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1972 / Guidebooks EA131
Frances Loeb Library Guide / Brochures AA034
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1982-1983 / Guidebooks EA129
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1983-1984 / Guidebooks EA129
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1984-1985 / Handbooks EA128
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1985-1986 / Handbooks EA128
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1985-1986 / Inventories EA098
Frances Loeb Library Guide, 1986-1987 / Handbooks EA128
Frances Loeb Library Handbook / Handbooks EA128
Frances Loeb Library Manuscipts Manual / Manuals (instructional materials) EA074
Frances Loeb Library Users' Guide / Brochures EA104
Frances Loeb Library Users' Guide, 1977 / Guidebooks EA130, EA131
Frances Loeb Library Users' Guide, 1978 / Guidebooks EA130, EA131
Frances Loeb Library Users' Guide, 1980 / Guidebooks EA130
From Gund Hall to Timbuktu / Clippings BA005
Fullbright Grants Preliminary Information / Leaflets (printed works) FA023
Further Thoughts on Humanizing Gund Hall / Memorandums DA008, EA020
Future of the City: The Next Fifty Years / Brochures DB124
Gamut / Publications CC116, DC043
Gardner Urges End of City Rifts / Correspondence BA002
Gazette: The 350th Celebration / Newspapers DB117
Gender Studies Chair at Education School Held by Gilligan / Articles BA015
George Gund Hall / Brochures DA002, DB132
George Gund Hall / Pamphlets EB020
George Gund Hall / Programs (documents) BC068
George Gund Hall: A New Building for the GSD / Typescripts DA011
Gerald D. Hines Makes Gift to Support Instruction in Real Estate / Serials (publications) AA035
German Werkbund Reviewed / Clippings DB056
Ghosts Along the Mississippi / Correspondence CC034
Grading System Options: Interim Report on the Student/Faculty Task Group / Report AB002
Graduate School of Design Anniversary Program, 1986 / Publications CB008
Graduate School of Design at Harvard University: The Years Ahead / Writings (document genre) BB016
Graduate School of Design General Council and Departmental Representatives / Speeches BC061
Graduate School of Design Lecture and Exhibition Series / Brochures DB067, DB068
Graduate School of Design Organization of Faculty, 1993-1994 / Oganizational charts FA017
Graduates Specializing in Real Estate 2000 / Directories CC131
Granite Garden / Newsletters CA013
Granite Garden: Urban Nature and Human Design / Notebooks EA099
Gropius House / Publications CC023
Gropius Publications / Lists (document genres) BB040
Gropius Years / Typescripts DC032
GSD 1968-1969: A Review / Reports DB001
GSD Academic Calendar, 1993-1994 / Brochures FA018
GSD Academic Calendar, 1993-1994 / Leaflets (printed works) FA033
GSD Academic Calendar, 1994-1995 / Leaflets (printed works) FA032
GSD Academic Calendar, 1994-1995 / Memorandums FA006
GSD Academic Calendar, 1996-1997 / Leaflets (printed works) FA022
GSD Alumni / Newsletters BC039
GSD Alumni Council / Booklets BC153
GSD Alumni Directories / Catalogs AB000
GSD Annual Report, 2003 / Brochures AA025
GSD Annual Report, 2005 / Reports AA026
GSD Association Council / Booklets BC152
GSD Association Council / Brochures AA034
GSD at 50 / Newspapers AA042
GSD at Fifty / Gazettes DB128, DB131
GSD Building Program / Building programs EB015
GSD Calendar / Bulletins BC013, BC014, BC015, BC016
GSD Calendar / Calendars DC002, DC003
GSD Calendar / Newsletters BC041
GSD Calendar: This Week / Calendars DC001
GSD Catalog / Registers AB024
GSD Commencement Ceremony / Programs (documents) CB004
GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1993 / Bulletins FA015
GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1994 / Bulletins AB019
GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1996 / Bulletins FA025, FA061
GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1996 / Flyers (printed matter) FA067
GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1997 / Bulletins AB019
GSD Course Bulletin, Spring 1995 / Bulletins AB019
GSD Course Bulletin, Spring 1997 / Bulletins FA061
GSD Design Lines / Bibliographies FA042, FA050, FA063
GSD Design Lines / Newsletters BB036, FA045
GSD Development Campaigns / Xerographic copies BB029
GSD Directory, 1980-1981 / Telephone directories AA002
GSD Directory, 1981-1982 / Telephone directories AA002
GSD Directory, 1982-1983 / Telephone directories AA002
GSD Directory, 1983-1984 / Telephone directories AA004
GSD Directory, 1984-1985 / Telephone directories AA004
GSD Directory, 1985-1986 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory, Fall 1986 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory, Fall 1987 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory, Fall 1988 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory, Fall 1995 / Directories AB012
GSD Directory, Spring, 1987 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory, Spring, 1988 / Telephone directories AA005
GSD Directory Assistance, 1969 / Forms (information artifacts) BC060
GSD Donor Report, 2006 / Reports AA027
GSD Evening Courses for Professional Development, Fall 1986 / Booklets BB028
GSD Events, Spring 1994 / Leaflets (printed works) FA033
GSD Facebook / Brochures AA034
GSD Facebook, 1976-1977 / Facebooks AB025
GSD Facebook, 1977-1978 / Facebooks AB025
GSD Facebook, 1978-1979 / Facebooks AB025
GSD Facebook, 1979-1980 / Facebooks AB025
GSD Facebook, 1980-1981 / Facebooks AB026
GSD Facebook, 1981-1982 / Facebooks AB026
GSD Facebook, 1982-1983 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1983-1984 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1984-1985 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1985-1986 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1986-1987 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1987-1988 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1988-1989 / Facebooks AB027
GSD Facebook, 1989-1990 / Facebooks AB028
GSD Facebook, 1990-1991 / Facebooks AB028
GSD Facebook, 1991-1992 / Facebooks AB028
GSD Facebook, 1992-1993 / Facebooks AB028
GSD Facebook, 1993-1994 / Facebooks AB029
GSD Facebook, 1994-1995 / Booklets FA072
GSD Facebook, 1994-1995 / Facebooks AB029
GSD Facebook, 1995-1996 / Booklets FA072
GSD Facebook, 1995-1996 / Facebooks AB029
GSD Facebook, 1996-1997 / Booklets FA073
GSD Facebook, 1996-1997 / Facebooks AB029
GSD Facebook, 1997-1998 / Booklets FA073
GSD Facebook, 1997-1998 / Facebooks AB029
GSD Faculty and Staff, 1984-1985 / Booklets AA008
GSD Faculty and Staff, 1987-1988 / Booklets AA008, BB018
GSD Faculty and Staff Computing Handbook / Handbooks AB030
GSD Faculty Directory / Brochures AA034
GSD Fall Bulletin / Brochures AA034
GSD Financial Aid Handbook, 1984-1985 / Booklets AB008
GSD Financial Aid Handbook, 1985-1986 / Booklets AB009
GSD Footage Information / Lists (document genres) FB035
GSD Intensive Courses for Professional Development, Summer 1984 / Booklet BB032
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Fall 1981 / Brochures DC019, DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Fall 1982 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Fall 1985 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, November / December 1986 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Spring 1982 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Spring 1982 / Posters DB083
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Spring 1984 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Spring 1986 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lectures and Exhibitions, Spring 1987 / Brochures DC019
GSD Lecture Series, Spring 1977 / Brochures DC019
GSD Loeb Fellows / Brochures AA034
GSD News / Clippings BC154, DB081
GSD News / Newsletters BB036, BC043, BC054, DB095, DB114, FA055
GSD News / Photographs FB014
GSD News / Typescripts AA017
GSD Newsletter / Newsletters BC054
GSD News Notes / Bibliographies FA042, FA043
GSD News Notes / Brochures FA018
GSD News Notes / Clippings FA048
GSD News Notes / Flyers (printed matter) FA067
GSD News Notes / Lists (document genres) AA006
GSD News Notes / Memorandums FA006
GSD News Notes / Newsletters AA041, FA010, FA036, FA064
GSD News Notes / Typescripts AA017
GSD Official Registers / Catalogs AB000
GSD Prize Awarded for Transforming Rio Slums / Clippings BA009
GSD Professional Development Courses, Summer 1996 / Pamphlets BB030
GSD Publications / Lists (document genres) BB040
GSD Publications Series in Architecture / Brochures CB001
GSD Realism 1970 / Typescripts CC076
GSD Resources and Services / Brochures AA034
GSD Resources and Services, 1982-1983 / Academic prospectuses AA003
GSD Resources and Services, 1983-1984 / Academic prospectuses AA003
GSD Sheet / Bulletins BC038
GSD Staff Handbook / Handbooks AB020
GSD Staff Handbook, 1985-1986 / Employees' manuals AA007
GSD Staff Handbook, 1986-1987 / Employees' manuals AA007, AA009
GSD Staff Newsletter / Bibliographies FA014, FA051
GSD Staff Newsletter / Memorandums FA008
GSD Student / Newsletters DB096
GSD Student Computing Handbook / Handbooks AB030
GSD Student Council Papers, 1966-1967 / Catalogs AB000
GSD Student Directory, 1983-1984 / Booklets AB007
GSD Student Directory, 1984-1985 / Booklets AB008
GSD Student Handbook / Booklets AB010
GSD Student Handbook, 1980-1981 / Annual reports AA015
GSD Student Handbook, 1988-1989 / Booklets AB011
GSD Student Handbook, 1989-1990 / Handbooks AB021
GSD Student Handbook, 1990-1991 / Handbooks AB021
GSD Student Handbook, 1991-1992 / Handbooks AB022
GSD Student Handbook, 1992-1993 / Handbooks AB022
GSD Student Handbook, 1993-1994 / Handbooks AB022
GSD Student Handbook, 1994-1995 / Handbooks AB022
GSD Student Handbook, 1995-1996 / Handbooks AB022
GSD Student Handbook, 1996-1997 / Handbooks AB022, FA020
GSD Student Handbook, 2001-2002 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Handbook, 2002-2003 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Handbook, 2003-2004 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Handbook, 2004-2005 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Handbook, 2005-2006 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Handbook, 2006-2007 / Handbooks AB023
GSD Student Resources, 1981-1982 / Booklets AB006
GSD Students, 1986-1987 / Booklets FA071
GSD Student to Student Guide, 1985-1986 / Booklets AB009
GSD Telephone Directories, Fall 1994 / Telephone directories AB013
GSD Telephone Directories, Fall 1995 / Telephone directories AB013
GSD Telephone Directories, Spring 1994 / Telephone directories AB013
GSD Telephone Directories, Spring 1995 / Telephone directories AB013
GSD Telephone Directory / Directories FA062
GSD Telethon, 1982 / Brochures BB034
GSD This Week / Brochures FA018
GSD This Week / Newsletters FA011
GSD Today and Tomorrow / Brochures DB007
GSD Utopia 1960 / Typescripts CC076
GSD Utopia 1960; GSD Realism 1970 / Typescripts CC077, CC078, CC079
GSD Visiting Committee / Brochures AA034
GSD Visiting Committee, 1982-1983 / Booklets AA049
GSD Visiting Committee, 1983-1984 / Booklets AA049
GSD Visiting Committee, 1986-1987 / Booklets AA049
Guardian / Clippings DB092
Guide to Harvard University Library, 1990 / Leaflets (printed works) FA032
Guide to the Arthur A. Shurcliff Collection of Lantern Slides / Reports EA111
Guide to the Arts at Harvard and Radcliffe / Brochures FA021
Guide to the Frances Loeb Library / Brochures EA089
Guide to the Frances Loeb Library / Publications EA033
Guide to the Special Collections of the Frances Loeb Library / Brochures EA090
Gund Hall: Up in 30 Minutes / Clippings BA005
Gund Hall Dedication / Pamphlets EB020
Gund Hall Dedication. October 12-13, 1972 / Newsletters BC062
Gund Hall Dedication Addresses / Speeches DA001
Gund Hall Facilities Renovation Program / Press releases AA038
Gund Hall Facility Condition Assessment / Reports EB017
Gund Hall Facility Condition Assessment Program / Reports EB018
Gund Lectures and Exhibitions, 1978-1979 / Press releases DC005, DC006
H.H. Richardson Collection / Memorandums FA008
Halprin Delivers Olmsted Lecture / Booklets DB064
Han's Scharoun's Berlin Philarmonic Hall Notebook / Typescripts CC093
Happy Birthday, John Harvard / Magazines (periodicals) DB121
Harvard's 350th Anniversary Celebration: Calendar of Events / Schedules (time plans) DB099
Harvard's 350th Anniversary Celebration. Schedule of Events and Application Materials / Magazines (periodicals) DB094
Harvard's Experiment on Mt. Auburn Stree / Clippings BA008
Harvard's Landscape Architecture Program Turns 100 / Lists (document genres) BA006
Harvard 350th: a Booklist / Brochures DB129
Harvard Alumni Bulletin / Newsletters BC029
Harvard Alumni Bulletin / Photographs FB044, FB047
Harvard and Money: a Memorandum on Issues and Choices / Brochures BC065
Harvard and the Changing World, 350th Anniversary Celebration of the Founding of Harvard College / Brochures DB104
Harvard Anniversary Summary / Brochures DB104
Harvard Architecture Review / Newsletters CA005, CA006, CA015
Harvard as Seen in Its Buildings / Articles BA023
Harvard at 350: The Nation's Oldest University Celebrates a Birthday / Publications CB010
Harvard Builds Boston / Gazettes DC037
Harvard Bulletin / Publications BB037
Harvard City Planning Studies / Brochures CB001
Harvard Crimson / Clippings BA005
Harvard Crimson / Newsletters BC054
Harvard Crimson / Newspapers DB090, DB091, DB108, DB122
Harvard Crimson: Special Commemorative Edition / Magazines (periodicals) DB133, DB134
Harvard Crimson: Special Commemorative Edition. 350 Years of Harvard / Publications CB009
Harvard Design Magazine / Flyers (printed matter) FA060
Harvard Design School Facts / Brochures EA104
Harvard Design School Guide to Shopping / Articles BA020
Harvard Factor: The University Celebrates Its 350th Anniversary / Magazines (periodicals) DB111
Harvard Gazette / Bibliographies FA014
Harvard Gazette / Booklets BB018
Harvard Gazette / Clippings BA005
Harvard Gazette / Gazettes DB131
Harvard Gazette / Press releases CC139
Harvard Gazette Supplement / Gazettes DB131
Harvard Gazzette Supplement / Gazettes DB128
Harvard Graduate School of Design / Academic prospectuses AA010
Harvard Graduate School of Design / Pamphlets EB020
Harvard Graduate School of Design: Directions for the Near Future / Lectures BB026
Harvard Graduate School of Design: Directions for the Near Future / Publications CC123
Harvard Graduate School of Design. Complete Building Program. December 4, 1967 / Reports DA007
Harvard Graduate School of Design. Development Program: The New Building / Pamphlets EB020
Harvard Graduate School of Design Alumni/ae Directory Supplement, 1976 / Directories BC156
Harvard Graduate School of Design Association Newsletter, see also HGSDA Newsletter / Newsletters BC039
Harvard Graduate School of Design Guide to Shopping / Articles BA023
Harvard Graduate School of Design Reunion, 1954 -1958 / Brochures BC155
Harvard Independent. 350th Birthday Issue / Newspapers DB098
Harvard Jerusalem Studio: Urban Design for the Holy City / Notebooks EA099
Harvard Lampoon / Magazines (periodicals) DB106
Harvard Librarian / Publications BC011
Harvard Magazine / Magazines (periodicals) AA043, DB094, DB121
Harvard Magazine / Publications BB038
Harvard Pays $1 Million For Design School Tract / Manuscripts DA012
Harvard Real Estate Symposium Hails Local Land-Use Planning / Articles BA012
Harvard Salient: A Journal of Conservative Thought / Journals (periodicals) DB097
Harvard Students Devise Villa Scheme / Articles BA012
Harvard Today / Clippings DB049
Harvard Today / Newspapers BC036
Harvard University, The President's Report, 1954-1955 / Annual reports AA013
Harvard University: An Architectural Tour / Articles BA023
Harvard University. Graduate School of Design. Anniversary Program / Programs (documents) DB120
Harvard University. Harvard and the Changing World. 350th Anniversary Celebration of the Founding of Harvard College / Brochures DB119
Harvard University's 350th Anniversary Celebrations: Official Program / Brochures DB129
Harvard University 350th Anniversary: Stadium Celebration / Programs (documents) DB101
Harvard University Alumni Day. 350th Anniversary Celebration of Harvard College / Programs (documents) DB093
Harvard University Foundation Day. 350th Anniversary Celebration of Harvard College / Programs (documents) DB093
Harvard University Foundation Day. 350th Anniversary Celebration of the Founding of Harvard College / Brochures DB119
Harvard University Gazette / Clippings FA048
Harvard University Gazette / Forms (documents) BC091
Harvard University Gazette / Gazettes DC037, FA047
Harvard University Gazette / Newsletters CC075
Harvard University Gazette / Press releases BC094
Harvard University Gazette: Commencement 1996 / Gazettes FA028
Harvard University Gazette: The 350th Celebration / Newspapers DB117
Harvard University Gazzette / Articles BA015
Harvard University Gazzette Supplement / Newspapers AA042
Harvard University Graduate School of Design: Alumni/ae Directory, 1992 / Alumni directories BB042
Harvard University Graduate School of Design: Alumni/ae Directory, 1997 / Alumni directories BB043
Harvard University Graduate School of Design: Anniversary Program / Programs (documents) DB100
Harvard University Library / Publications BC011
HGSDA Constitution / Memorandums BC006
HGSDA Council, 1981-1982 / Booklets BC152
HGSDA Council, 1982-1983 / Booklets BC152
HGSDA Council, 1983-1984 / Booklets BC152
HGSDA Council, 1984-1985 / Booklets BC153
HGSDA Council, 1985-1986 / Booklets BC153
HGSDA Dedication Review / Newsletters BC062
HGSDA News / Bills BC081
HGSDA News / Clippings DB042